[{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678994789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7352,"timeElapsed":113064},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679000730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5939,"timeElapsed":119007},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679004874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4142,"timeElapsed":123151},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679011585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6709,"timeElapsed":129862},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679020807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9219,"timeElapsed":139084},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679029287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8477,"timeElapsed":147564},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679038750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9461,"timeElapsed":157027},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679044312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5559,"timeElapsed":162589},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679049579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5264,"timeElapsed":167856},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679061089,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9763,"timeElapsed":179366},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679063787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2696,"timeElapsed":182064},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679066377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2588,"timeElapsed":184654},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679070112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3733,"timeElapsed":188389},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679073026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2911,"timeElapsed":191302},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679077128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4100,"timeElapsed":195405},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679079726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2596,"timeElapsed":198003},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679084428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4700,"timeElapsed":202705},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679090530,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6097,"timeElapsed":208805},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679095596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5064,"timeElapsed":213873},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679102258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4883,"timeElapsed":220535},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679104591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2331,"timeElapsed":222868},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679106737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2143,"timeElapsed":225014},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679109839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3100,"timeElapsed":228115},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679112428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2587,"timeElapsed":230705},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679114798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2366,"timeElapsed":233074},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679117035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2235,"timeElapsed":235312},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679120213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3176,"timeElapsed":238490},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679122715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2499,"timeElapsed":240992},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679131316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7511,"timeElapsed":249593},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679133522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2204,"timeElapsed":251799},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679135684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2159,"timeElapsed":253961},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679138354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2668,"timeElapsed":256631},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679140571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2216,"timeElapsed":258848},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679144602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4029,"timeElapsed":262879},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679147544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2940,"timeElapsed":265821},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679149858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2311,"timeElapsed":268135},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679152432,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2572,"timeElapsed":270709},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679159297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5646,"timeElapsed":277574},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679161879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2580,"timeElapsed":280155},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679164092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2212,"timeElapsed":282369},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679167239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3144,"timeElapsed":285515},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679169620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2379,"timeElapsed":287897},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679171837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2215,"timeElapsed":290114},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679174267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2427,"timeElapsed":292544},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679177065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2796,"timeElapsed":295342},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679179346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2280,"timeElapsed":297623},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679186073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5340,"timeElapsed":304350},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679188482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2407,"timeElapsed":306759},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679190544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2060,"timeElapsed":308821},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679194359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3813,"timeElapsed":312636},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679196560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2199,"timeElapsed":314837},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679198980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2418,"timeElapsed":317257},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679200918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1937,"timeElapsed":319195},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679203484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2564,"timeElapsed":321761},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679205518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2031,"timeElapsed":323794},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679212750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6025,"timeElapsed":331026},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679214843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2091,"timeElapsed":333120},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679217116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2272,"timeElapsed":335393},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679219098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1979,"timeElapsed":337374},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679221251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2150,"timeElapsed":339528},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679223272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2019,"timeElapsed":341549},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679225529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2255,"timeElapsed":343806},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679227574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2043,"timeElapsed":345851},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679229688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2111,"timeElapsed":347965},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679257872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":27149,"timeElapsed":376149},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679259993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2119,"timeElapsed":378270},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679262239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2244,"timeElapsed":380516},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679264929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2688,"timeElapsed":383206},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679267190,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2259,"timeElapsed":385467},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679269488,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2295,"timeElapsed":387765},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679271501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2012,"timeElapsed":389778},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679273407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1903,"timeElapsed":391683},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679275636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2228,"timeElapsed":393913},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679277773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2135,"timeElapsed":396050},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679283522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4581,"timeElapsed":401799},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679285571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2047,"timeElapsed":403848},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679287721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2148,"timeElapsed":405998},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679290322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2599,"timeElapsed":408599},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679292416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2091,"timeElapsed":410693},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679294537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2119,"timeElapsed":412814},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679296535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1995,"timeElapsed":414811},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679298895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2359,"timeElapsed":417172},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679300878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1981,"timeElapsed":419155},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679308272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":6127,"timeElapsed":426549},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679310325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2051,"timeElapsed":428602},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679312422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2096,"timeElapsed":430699},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679314804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2380,"timeElapsed":433081},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679316949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2143,"timeElapsed":435226},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679319083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2131,"timeElapsed":437359},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679321196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2111,"timeElapsed":439473},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679323225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2027,"timeElapsed":441502},{"subjectID":"5zss2u5vyu","prolificID":"66553eb5f10b5700001d20de","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b44d69061419d7e947c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679325138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1911,"timeElapsed":443415}]